contussupport.com 2018-10-04

# Contus Privacy Policies

## Privacy Policy 

**Information that we collect and how we use it**

Contus respects your privacy and is committed to protect the information you provide us through this website. We do not sell or distribute user information to third parties unless it is legally required. We gather user information in order to serve your needs and respond to your information requests.

**Data Security Compliance**

The security and privacy of your data is a crucial part of Contus business. This statement provides our clients, the assurance and our commitment to information & data security compliance. We are committed to respect your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us. Contus focuses on continual improvement of its privacy policy.

**Collecting User Information**

We collect information about our web visitors indirectly through our Internet access logs. When you access Contus, the browser's domain name and Internet address is automatically collected and placed in our Internet access logs. We use this information to learn about which sections, pages and information web site visitors access.

**Usage of Personal Information**

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address and an email address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Contus Web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.

If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the web, we may transfer that Information within Contus or to Contus third-party service providers, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.

Contus strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Contus intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy even if, in connection with the above, we transfer your Personal Information from your country to countries that may not require an "adequate" level of protection for your Personal Information. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that Personal Information is collected, transferred, or retained.

**Cookies**

Contus website may use cookies to assist in producing overall site visitor statistics. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to find out the identity of any user unless they specifically tell us who they are. If you wish to, you can disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in preferences or options menu in your browser.

**Disclosure of User Information**

Contus does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with non-affiliated party or companies. If you have submitted user information to us through an e-mail, Contus maintains your security by ensuring that the information is only distributed within the Contus Group who are all responsible for responding to your requests either directly or indirectly.

**We may disclose information in the following circumstances**

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Contus under extremely strict confidentiality agreements.
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

**Links to Third Party Sites**

Contus website may provide links to other third party websites. Contus is not responsible for the contents or policies of these websites. These links are provided to you for convenience purposes only and Contus is not liable for inaccuracy of any information on such sites. These sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. If the Contus website links you to any third-party website, we make no representation as to the existence, sufficiency, accuracy or completeness of their Privacy Policy.

**Disclosure of User Information**

The products, technology and services described in this site may be the subject of intellectual property rights reserved by Contus or other third parties. Nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring to you in any manner, whether by implication, estoppel or otherwise, any license, title or ownership of or to any intellectual property right of Contus or any third party.
